[Music] Do
you have insurance? Don't be fooled. Let's
talk.
Good life to all of you.
Come on, join me.
Let's review the FWD product. That's the set
for tomorrow. What is the set for tomorrow?
This is a term insurance program that is renewable
every 5 or 10 years. It is plain, simple, and
direct to the point.
It doesn't have savings and investment
features. So it has three variants:
the Short term cover, income protector,
and the Estate protector. In this video,
we will talk about the
short term cover variant. So what are the
benefits and coverage? Number one is the
life insurance. The minimum coverage is 4
million for a 25-year-
old. That's a lot. No, 4 million right away at
age 25. Number two, terminal illness
benefit. Advance the life insurance
benefit when diagnosed with a terminal
illness. The insured will not have to
wait for the insured to die.
The proceeds will be given to him/her immediately.
Number three, child protection.
An additional 100% of the coverage will be
given to the minor beneficiary when
his/her parent or
spouse dies, even if only one of them dies.  to them the
insured or those who take this
program as long as they die in the same
accident whether one came first
the other came later as long as the cause is the same the
100% of the
coverage will be given to the minor
beneficiary of the child number 4 overseas
benefit if the insured dies
abroad whether he is an OFW or tourist an
additional 20% or
500,000 whichever is lower the bay that
proceeds to the beneficiary will be given first
life insurance coverage plus the 20% or
500,000 whichever is lower
number 5 funeral assistance
advance 10% of your
coverage maximum of
100,000 for the initial expenses
of the family within
48 hours two days while waiting for
the full proceeds so this is good because
we know that if there is debt, then that is
accompanied by
expenses so we can avoid borrowing
from others or selling or withdrawing
our savings for the initial
expenses because within 48 hours the
funeral assistance will be received
beneficiary so this is
[Music]
will be added then given so at least
we will have some money to spend in the first
Uh first days how many years can you
take this minimum of age minimum age
is 25 to 55 years old and it is renewable
until age 75 when
you took it every 5 years when you took it every 10 years the
coverage you took is You can
renew it until age 70 what are the
requirements to apply of course at least
25 years old to 55 years old
you must also have a valid ID available and of
course there is a fee Is this
subject to incontestability provision
Yes after 2 years so within 2 years
we can just wait for notification from
fwd then that's the time we can say that
our insurance is effective
How much is the premium It depends on the amount
of coverage but the minimum is
12,000 So if your budget is less
than 12,000 a year Ah you can't avail
it because the minimum premium is
12,000 a year or 3,367
so who is
this program for number one for bread winners
who need At least 900,000 worth
of life insurance
coverage number two have enough income
to pay the minimum premium
quarterly number three for those who
want to add their life
insurance coverage because their
family's needs have grown or maybe
they have a mortgage or a home loan ah car
loan or any type of loan number four
for those who want plain simple
and affordable yet High value life
insurance coverage number five for
those who treat
their insurance premiums as an expense not savings
not investment because it has no
living benefit if you pay the 5
years 10 years or you finish it
you will not receive any cash
benefit What is the disadvantage the minimum
premium is 12,000 annually or that's
3360 quarterly maybe to others
that's small but the majority of Filipinos are
only on the minimum wage that's around 34,000
or
344 a day to  570 a day or 600 or the other
700 per
day that's around 88% to 13% of our
annual income so that 12,000 per annum will
eat up 8 to 13% of our annual
income it's a bit high compared to
our recommended At least 3 to 5%
Only a cent of your annual income should
be allocated to your
premium number two limited to death
benefit and terminal illness benefit
There is no other coverage like critical
illness hospital income benefit What else is there
Accidental Deb benefit
um What else are there many other types of
Riders so it doesn't have it because it's plain and
simple number three its
coverage is only up to a maximum of 5 million
if you take it via online
because you can take it via online
number four the premium increases
every 5 or 10 years It depends on the program
you took So what are
its advantages number one High coverage
and low cost versus other programs so
I would consider it personally
its coverage is cheap and high number
two for as low as
Your life insurance coverage is Php3,000 lion if you enroll at
age 25 number
three you can avail it via online so
therefore you don't need to go through
an insurance Agent especially if
you don't want to be interfered with in
your decisions when it comes to insurance
planning can I recommend him
Of course yes but there are things
we need to consider so number
one do you really need
insurance
answer number two what type of insurance
coverage do you need if
you really need it number 3 how much
coverage do you really need
number 4 until when do you really
need it number five can
your budget really afford the future premiums number
six what are the guiding principles that
you have in getting life insurance so
our advice is still it is best to
talk to a professional insurance
advisor if we plan to get
our life insurance I believe that
a professional insurance
advisor has the ability to give
us the right insurance program based
on our needs and more importantly
can our budget afford it so that
we don't get stressed about our future premiums
If in  Do you think you are ready to
get a set for tomorrow by fwd?
Apply for this program via this link
or message us for
your insurance planning. Have a good
life and I hope
this video was helpful to you. If you want more
content like this, follow ipr cooperative
[Music]